Guide to the Records of the Alumni Federation of New York University, Inc. RG.40.7
New York University Archives
- Series III: Affiliated Alumni Groups & Activities
  - Football Dinner, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - NYU Letter Club Activities, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Nebraska - NYU Football Game Trip, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Activities - Bermuda Cruise, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - New York University Centennial Fund, 1926-1928 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Chancellor's Alumni Meeting, May 22, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - New York University Community Relations, 1926-1928 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Chancellor's Committee on Alumni Opinion, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - New York Conference of Universities, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Purchase of Original NYU Diploma, 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Ohio State - NYU Football Game and Trip, October 3, 1936, 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - NYU Tennis Club 1900-1927, circa 1927 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Newman Club, 1931-1934 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Occupational Lists, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Lawrence House Student Union, YMCA, 1932-1935 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Bureau of Employment, 1923-1929 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - New York Alumni Club of Delta Sigma Pi, 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - New York Alumni Club of Delta Sigma Pi, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Alpha Kappa Psi Fraternity, 1936-1938 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Stationery, circa 1937 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Phi Gamma Delta - General, 1935-1940 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Phi Gamma Delta - General, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Directories, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Association Records and Correspondence, 1936-1941 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Audit, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - George Kastener Correspondence and Addresses/Paper Clippings (Secretary), 1936-1940 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Charles D. Haughey Correspondence (Treasurer), 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "Hall of Fame Fiji": Nu Epsilon Chapter of Phi Gamma Delta, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Phi Gamma Delta 50th Anniversary, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Activities, 1936-1940 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Phi Gamma Delta National Office (1 of 2), 1936-1941 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Phi Gamma Delta National Office (2 of 2), 1936-1941 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Chapter Materials, 1938-1941 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Phi Gamma Delta General Correspondence, 1936-1940 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 2274 Loring Place, Morrison and Lynn Attorneys, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 2274 Loring Place, Fire Insurance, 1936-1939 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Alumni Bartley to Loughran, 1936-1940 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Alumni Mautel to Young, 1936-1940 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Oversized Materials and Ephemera, 1926-1938 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Series IV: Correspondence
  Series IV includes correspondence of various alumni and officers associated with the Alumni Federation.
  - Alexander F. Makay & Company, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Barr, Jean B., Supervisor of Printing, 1920-1932 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Badger, Phillip O., Professor of Marketing, 1925-1935 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Briesen, Fritz, Law '97, 1924-1934 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Broderick, Joseph, Commerce '06, 1925-1933 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Brown, Samuel A., Medicine '94, 1924-1934 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Chase, Harry Woodburn, Chancellor, 1933-1935 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Clyne, James F., Editor "New York University Alumnus" (1 of 3), 1933-1940 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Clyne, James F., Editor "New York University Alumnus" (2 of 3), 1933-1940 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Clyne, James F., Editor "New York University Alumnus" (3 of 3), 1933-1940 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Draper, Arthur S., Engineering '05, 1925-1932 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Draper, Arthur S., Engineering '05, 1932-1936 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Fernald, Henry B., Arts '01, 1921-1934 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - General, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Garvin, Edwin L., Arts '97 and Law '99, 1925-1932 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Hendershot, W. Raymond, Commerce '20, 1925-1930 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Irwin, John V., Arts '94 and Law '99, 1923-1931 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Irwin, John V., Arts '94 and Law '99, 1931-1934 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jones, Theodore F., Director of Heights Library and Professor of History, 1925-1931 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Kent, Fred I., University Council, 1931-1935 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Kimball, Leroy E., Comptroller, 1923-1935 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Kingsley, William M., Arts '84, 1924-1935 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Larsen, George, Arts '06, 1922-1936 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Makay, Alexander F., Commerce '09 (1 of 2), 1923-1931 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Makay, Alexander F., Commerce '09 (2 of 2), 1923-1931 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Makay, Alexander F., Commerce '09, 1931-1934 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Onderdonk, Charles D., Office Manager, 1927-1935 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Patterson, William M., Law '93 (1 of 2), 1926-1936 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Patterson, William M., Law '93 (2 of 2), 1926-1936 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Patterson, William M., Law '93 (1 of 2), 1936-1938 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Patterson, William M., Law '93 (2 of 2), 1936-1938 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Patterson, William M., Law '93 (1 of 2), 1933-1936 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Patterson, William M., Law '93 (2 of 2), 1933-1936 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Roberts, Vincent, 1921-1932 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Roberts, Vincent, 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Ross, Benjamin A., Alumni Federation Secretary (1 of 2), 1927-1934 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Ross, Banjamin A., Alumni Federation Secretary (2 of 2), 1927-1934 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Saunders, Richard P., 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sommer, Frank H., Dean of Law School, 1924-1934 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Tompkins, Leslie J., Law '92, 1925-1935 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Voorhis, Harold O., NYU Secretary (1 of 2), 1924-1932 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Voorhis, Harold O., NYU Secretary (2 of 2), 1924-1932 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Voorhis, Harold O., NYU Secretary, 1932-1936 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Washburn, Earle L., NYU Auditor, 1923-1935 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Unprocessed materials
  - Unprocessed notecards (Box 20)